stretching
leads to another question.
But I don't feel afraid anymore.
There
else
where
matter. Now I can hear my own voice
above the noise.
Live your life with your eyes on the
horizon.
Keep moving even when progress feels
invisible.
The things we're protecting are already
around you. The people beside you are
proof that you're not alone.
Give everything you have to this moment.
Leave nothing trapped inside your heart.
Every dream begins as something
impossible until someone decides to
believe in it.
Check it, [__] The werewolf pony in
front of us is getting the Starbucks
tropical butterfly refresher just like
us. It really is a small world.
Hello. Me and my black sister would like
two of your finest Starbucks tropical
butterfly refreshers, please.
>> Sorry, we just sold our last one. Would
you like to try one of our affordable $9
coffees instead?
>> What an unfortunate coincidence.
>> No, that werewolf pony buying that
Starbucks tropical butterfly refresher
was a statement and a front towards God
herself. If he didn't buy it, I would
have my own Starbucks Tropical Butterfly
Refresher for $7.75.
Even if the beverage remained, one of us
would not have received one regardless.
Call the Royal Guard ponies and tell
them this is a friendship level threat
alert. I am going to do the most natural
thing possible in this situation. I will
bulldo this Starbucks down and build a
monster school on top of it. We shall
gather every vampire, zombie, and
werewolf in Equestria and enroll them
immediately. Then teach them how to be
more normal like conversion camps do
with the gays.
Why are you still awake, you little
[__] Don't you know it's almost
midnight?
>> Look, Daddy, I drew us.
>> Hot damn, that looks like a steaming
pile of poopy up in this piece of ass.
I'm not putting that on the fridge.
Wait, are those my limited edition
crayons I bought from a flea market in
Ohio that I used to write autographs to
sexy [__] with big butts? Or hell no.
I'm going to beat your ass for the 12th
time this week, you stupid 4year-old
child.
>> Daddy, no.
>> Oh,
>> daddy. When are mommy and Trixie going
to come back?
>> I don't know, [__] Hey, I'm going to
be home late tonight.
So, I'm not making you anything to eat
again because I never do. If you get
hungry, there's about a/4 cup of spam
left in the garbage can that I didn't
eat because it had mold on it. Eat that
if you get hungry, [__]
>> Dad, it's Halloween. Let's carve some
pumpkins and make jacko'lanterns
together.
Can't. I'm going to be out all night
training the new male ponies. Turn the
lights off and keep quiet when you get
back home. I don't want
trick-or-treaters thinking we're awake.
Marionette, what the hell is this?
>> Oh, it's nothing. It's like a joke
thing. Someone at school gave it to me.
I was going to throw it away.
>> Do you think I'm stupid?
>> I don't even like girls. They gave it to
me and I just didn't want to make it
awkward, so I kept it. I was going to
get rid of it. Dad,
>> you are such a disappointment. Maybe I
should just put you somewhere you can be
fixed, like the ranch from the Dr. Phil
show.
And where exactly do you think you're
going?
>> I'm staying over at Starlights for a
while.
>> That confused lesbian.
>> She's not confused. She knows exactly
who she is. The only one confused is me.
And she says, "You're the reason why."
>> Is that what she told you, [__]
>> Yes. And she's right. Because you don't
let me have any hobbies.
So, I don't even have any friends.
>> Sorry, I didn't hear you over the sound
of me [__] myself.
>> Never mind, it's not important.
>> Then hurry up and get out of my house,
dumbass. I already looked on Google for
that fat [__] Dr. Phil's phone number.
So, you better be out of here in like 2
and 1/2 minutes if you don't want to end
up on the ranch, you stupid lesbian
[__]
>> Uh, okay. Wow, there's way more people
here than I thought. Hello everybody.
>> You got this, girl, boss. So, um, this
next song I'll be singing for you
tonight is heavily inspired by my
relationship with my girlfriend in the
front row, Starlight Glimmer.
>> It's called Please Don't Be Mad at Me
Again. It's not like a breakup song or
anything. I just write about emotions a
lot. And Starlight makes me feel a lot
of things.
She says she loves me
with the same mouth that tears me aart.
One second she's kissing my forhead in
the kitchen, the next she's asking why I
make everything diffult.
Why I can't just be normal? Why I always
look scared around her?
I started apologizing
automatically
for the things I don't even understand.
>> Stop looking. She isn't even singing
about me. I'm just an innocent little
lesbian.
>> She calls herself a
sharp and untouchable.
Sometimes
she grabs my wrist too hard. There's a
lipstick
stain on my hoodie and fingerprints on
my throat. And somehow
she left.
So, what did you think of my song?
>> I hated it. You made me sound like Adolf
Hitler.
>> You told me to sing about you.
>> Obviously, I just meant the cool [__]
that will make me look good, not our
dysfunctional relationship.
>> You think our relationship is
dysfunctional?
>> Not is was. I'm breaking up with you
again.
>> So, I take it you don't want to ride
home together then?
>> Okay, never mind. We're back together.
>> Okay, but I lost my wallet. So, we're
going to need to split the Uber cost.
>> Gotcha, [__]
>> Starlight, help me.
>> This is kind of exciting how Trixie,
it's like when we went to Celestia's
school for gifted unicorns. Yeah, except
I'm not pushing you into lockers or
taking a smelly dump on your shoes.
>> This place smells like blood,
cigarettes, and poop. Truly, this is a
school for horses. Like, oh my god,
Trixie, you became a vampire, too.
>> Lavender, Fuchsia, Twilight, these bad
[__] are my old school band mates
from middle school.
>> We pretended to be Trixiey's friend
because she had no friends. And hanging
out with the one balding loser in class
gave us increased moral superiority over
our enemies.
>> Haha, Lavender, you've always been a
jokester.
>> Oh, that's really cool. What kind of
music did you girls make?
>> Sorry, Twilight music is kind of like
our thing, not yours.
>> Yeah, like no offense, puppy girl, but I
don't think a mut like you has the ear
for sick tunes, especially ones that
smell like wet dog. I guess we'll catch
you later. Girl, why are you hanging
around a werewolf? Yeah, you know,
crossdating is weird. Werewolves are
like black people in the monster world.
Every click here hates every other
click. That's the whole monster
ecosystem.
Why did you let them talk to you like
that? Go back over there and maul their
butts off. After careful analysis, I
have concluded that for Trixie to
maintain a sustainable relationship
between her and her friends, it requires
strategic distancing on my part because
I am a deep purple, which makes me more
targetable by racist [__]
You forgot my luggage,
>> Mary. I forgot you're a werewolf, too.
Lord have mercy her, but cheeks are
glistening like two really big pearls.
>> Oh, hi, Twilight. Celestia stuffed me in
a giant sock at 3:00 in the morning and
drove me here herself. Have you seen
Starlight anywhere?
>> Not just your fat ass eye. I mean just
your but I mean never mind. Flawless, go
play. I'm going with Mary to get us all
checked into the dorms.
>> Hey, miscellaneous monster girl over
here.
What is this? The area for social
rejects?
>> That's literally what this is. So sit
your ass down before the rest of the
monster ecosystem notices you're alone.
You guys are really fine with calling
yourselves outcasts on purpose. Well,
it's not like we have much of a choice,
do we? We got abandoned by society the
minute Celestia put us in here and
confused us with monsters. See the
vampires over there? They think they're
superior to everyone because they're
immortal and hot. And the zombie
football team always hangs out near the
cafeteria because half of them are
literally falling apart and need
constant snacks. And it's in a
werewolf's nature to travel in packs.
Probably why your own mom ditched you at
the drop of a hat to go and fend for
yourself out here. Ghosts mostly hang
out over there.
>> I don't see them.
>> Well, yeah, they're ghosts. Why would
you be able to see them?
>> Then there's us. racial ambiguity, baby.
The ones no group wants to claim. Which
means if you don't sit with us, you're
not going to have anyone to talk to all
semester.
For the fifth time, Principal Celestia,
I'm not a dwarf. My height is just
slightly below the national stallion
average. I shouldn't even be in this
school.
>> You know, you remind me very much of
Princess Trixie Bell, whom I bullied a
[__] ton back in middle school. You
wouldn't happen to be
>> Princess Trixie Bell. Nope. Can't Can't
say it rings any bells.
>> I'm going to try and say this without it
sounding weird. Trixie Bell.
>> It's just Belle now. Please don't dead
name me.
>> I'm going to try and say this without it
sounding weird. Trixie Bell.
>> And you're going to ignore everything I
just said?
>> I'm going to try and say this without it
sounding weird. Trixie Bell. You're
exactly 83.5 cm tall, which happens to
be the exact same height as the human
male's crotch. It's like God explicitly
built you to suck off human males or
some [__] That fact alone places you in
a troubling situation when it comes to
the sexual hierarchy in this school,
especially for a stallion like you who
wishes to be viewed as what some may
call an alpha male.
>> I think 83.5 cm is a perfectly
respectable height for a grown man.
Well, I'm glad you think so because your
medical records show that your penis is
almost half the size of the national
average, too. So, I'm going to put down
that you still qualify as a dwarf.
Thankfully, you won't have trouble
finding ways to spend your time because
I already signed you up for the football
team.
>> Cool beans. Every pony is going to think
I'm masculine as [__]
>> Now, this is where I belong.
>> Hey guys, look. It's that pisscolored
horse Celestia said she was going to
send us for the football team.
>> Oh yeah. What tipped you off? Was it my
bulging muscles?
>> No, it was your really fat ass. And you
look like a raging fat. Put this on and
shake your butt for us before I beat the
[__] out of you, [__]
>> What? No, I'm supposed to play football
with the guys, not dance around in a
skirt. That's what the [__] are for.
They're supposed to be the ones dancing
for me.
>> No, man. Celestia put you on the cheer
squad to shake your butt.
>> I am not going to throw cheeks like a
[__] Men aren't supposed to wear
skirts and panties.
>> I get enough homophobic remarks from my
parents at home for my sin of being gay.
I will not tolerate them from you as
well.
>> This is so gay.
>> Put some more sauce into it, [__]
Yeah, shake that ass harder.
You can dance
every time of your life
again.
God, this is so freaking gay. Wait a
minute. Is this the type of [__] girls
have to go through on a daily basis
simply to exist as an object of men's
lust? Holy [__] Are we the bad guys?
>> Why is everyone in school so afraid of
her? She's been going around telling
everyone that she's got a salt spear,
which is a tool used to keep monsters at
bay. It's basically a weapon made of
salt. To summon one, you have to do a
ritual that requires four hearts being
placed at the corners of a salt circle.
One vampire, one werewolf, and one
zombie. Oh, and one from a mortal, too.
The salt spear is apparently like super
lethal to us monsters, so they're banned
because even the tiniest scratch can
pull all of the sodium out of the
victim's body like a magnet and turn
them into dust. Think of it like spicy
foods for white people or a black person
being told to follow rules or an Asian
person getting the belt on the ass for
getting a B on their math test. But we
don't have to worry. She only claims to
have one to instill fear and rule the
school. No one does except Celestia, and
it's locked away in the principal's
office when she's not using it to murder
us for fun. HA.
>> Today we are discussing casual racism.
Can some pony explain why vampires and
werewolves hate each other? Manar swirl
the bearded you got some fat butt
cheeks. I can't imagine the size of the
turds you can shoot out into the toilet.
>> Do you want to nibble on the other side
of my bone? Is it a rib? I'm not quite
sure. Probably a femur.
>> No thanks.
>> Sue to yourself. Oh my god, you are down
bad. You've been staring at her the
entire lecture. Trixie is just hanging
out with her friends.
>> I know. I'm just scared this whole
vampire and werewolf rivalry is going to
create a rift between us.
>> She's only enjoying herself. You should,
too. She's not worrying about you right
now. She trusts you. And I think you're
going to have a miserable semester if
you keep obsessing every time your
vampire wife talks to another monster.
Anyway, class is almost over. Why don't
we go hang out in the dorms?
You know, I think things will be fine.
Trixie talks about you constantly when
we're together.
>> Yeah, there it is. That embarrassing
little smile she loves so much. Hey, can
I ask you something weird?
>> Sure. Am I cute?
>> Yeah, you look pretty nice, I suppose.
>> Are you only saying that because I'm
Trixie's twin?
>> If you didn't already love somebody with
my face, would I still be pretty with a
face like this?
>> Why are you asking me something like
that?
>> I saw Trixie getting compliments today,
but I didn't get any. Is it because of
my scars? Am I hard to look at?
Starlight says the burns are the only
thing people notice about me. Even when
I wear expensive clothes and makeup, no
one seems to care. Is she right? Sorry,
Mary, but unfortunately I cannot relate
for I have been on the cover of the
magazine series Ponyville's Sexiest
Horse for 9 years in a row. Granted, my
teacher Celestia is the one who chooses
the winner, but I still think my victory
should not be undermined as nepotism. I
won that position fair and square. Screw
you, Rainbow Dash. Screw you.
Are you getting a call?
>> I'm going to take this. Will you still
be here when I get back?
>> No. I'm going to go take a big smelly
poop.
>> Starlight, are you even listening?
>> Yes, I'm listening. Girly Pop.
>> No. Like, seriously, listen. The fur on
my ears already completely healed over.
My new werewolf regeneration jeans are
actually working.
>> What?
>> The burns on my face. The werewolf genes
are repairing the damaged tissue way
faster than we thought. By the end of
the week, I might look completely normal
and I won't have to hide behind a mask
anymore. That's That's awesome. Totally
awesome.
>> You don't sound very thrilled about it.
Why? Mary, come on. It's late. I'm home
in bed and you called me out of the blue
just to brag. It's incredibly
pretentious and unlike you. Also, I'm
tired.
I don't know. The scars never bothered
me. And the mask cost eight whole
dollars to make out of papier-mâché. So,
there goes all that money down the
drain. I don't know why you're so happy
about this kind of outcome, to be
perfectly honest. You literally told me
they made me hard to look at.
Why do you always have to bring that up?
I said that one time during an argument
after two margaritas. Well, whatever.
I'm happy for you, okay? Like,
seriously, babe. This is amazing. You're
going to be so pretty.
>> You mean I wasn't before?
>> Oh my god. Why are you always twisting
everything I say? Your scars never
mattered to me. Shut up and go to sleep
already.
Fractured catch.
>> I hate wearing pink. I want a manly
color like purple.
>> What makes purple a manly color?
>> That's the color of balls. No, it ain't.
That's just yours.
>> Dead ass. Well, at least now you two
morons know I'm not gay.
>> They just scored on us again.
>> Okay, you need to calm down.
>> Calm down. Your flabby man tits are
showing and we are losing by 58 points.
>> Only 58 points, which means it's still
anyone's game.
Maybe we wouldn't be so far behind if
you weren't getting [__] blocked by
Flawless every godamn time.
>> She slips in and out of the fourth
dimension. Every pony gets blocked by
Flawless.
>> You know what the real problem is?
>> The fact that you're about to blame
somebody else.
>> The fact that nobody here appreciates my
contributions.
>> You want to know what really brines my
pickle?
>> No one asked you, Dyke.
>> The fact that you lie all the time.
>> What have I ever lied about? You said
you were captain of your high school
basketball team 5 minutes ago, but the
truth is you can't play for [__]
>> That part is true, though. I just went
to a predominantly white school. Okay,
listen up you neurode divergent incelss.
If we're going to have a chance of
winning this game against those
extremist, agendadriven female
activists, we're going to have to put
together a new strategy that may help us
out. Play that cotton picker.
>> What? What did I say? Spike, you can't
say that word.
>> What word? Winning.
>> No, cotton picker.
>> Trixie,
>> what? I'm only repeating what he just
said.
>> Cotton picker isn't a slur. Now,
those are some real racial slurs.
>> Spike,
>> why are you the one getting mad? You're
Latino. You literally have the n-word
pass. And since we're on the same team,
I'm temporarily a part of your cartel
group.
>> One free point to the blue team for the
pink team's racism. Look [__] cotton
picker is just something I say when I am
referring to someone who is soft or
black.
>> Ignore those losers. Let's just finish
this match.
>> Actually, I don't think I want to play
anymore.
>> Hey, if the [__] walks, we win by
default.
>> Hey, what's wrong, [__] You have the
face of someone who just learned Sonic
Underground got cancelled after only 40
episodes. Some purple dragon with an
obvious buttlft made fun of me during
gym.
>> Okay.
>> He was teasing me because I'm black and
I'm also autistic. Do you know what it's
like to be born with two disabilities at
the same time?
>> No, I'm a white guy. Look, I'm not
prepared for something this heavy. I
just brought my sister Twilight Sparkle
a happy meal so she'd look cool at the
lunch table in 10. Damn, she kind of
looks familiar. Like really familiar.
Like Chrysalis. Actually, she really
reminds me of Chrysalis. like a
suspicious ungodly amount. But she
doesn't look like a changeling. And
changelings don't drink pumpkin spice
lattes. That's some white girl [__]
Hey, I'm white. And her hair is No. No.
Lots of ponies have blue hair. Actually,
now that I think about it, I vaguely
remember having sex with the evil queen
Chrysalis like 10 or so times.
>> Why are you staring at me?
>> Changing drone 13,420.
Are you my daughter? You just figured
that out?
>> Okay, super cool. Dad mode activated.
And as your father, I have decided that
I am now qualified to be the solver of
racism.
>> Yeah,
>> look here. Changing drone 13,420.
When ponies make fun of you for being
black, it doesn't matter.
>> It doesn't? Why?
>> Because we all share the same struggles.
Like look at me for example. I'm white
and I had it way harder than you ever
did. Born in Canterlot, the richest city
in Equestria, just a measly seven figure
in my bank account before I could walk.
Graduated near the top of my class, so
naturally I was captain of the royal
guard. I got married to an olicorn
princess and lived in a castle. You
know, the same chances every pony is
given regardless of the color of their
fur. What about you?
>> My mom was Queen Chris Ellis.
>> Rough start, but go off queen. We moved
every few months because somebody was
always trying to arrest her. I think we
lived in a hollow log for 8 months, but
I can't really remember. When I was 4
weeks old, I got a rock for my birthday.
>> That's nice.
>> Oh, wait. I just remembered. I didn't
get a rock for my birthday. Someone
threw a rock at me for being black. And
it just so happened to be during my
birthday party, which was behind the
Kmart dumpster.
There he is. That's the man who made fun
of me. So, you like making little girls
cry, huh?
>> Yeah, I guess so.
What the hell?
>> Oh my god,
you're crazy. Give that to me. No. Let
go.
Do you have anything lowfat for like not
fat [__]
>> Don't waste your time, baby girl. I
already tried.
>> Twilight Sparkles older brother, what
are you doing here in the maximum
security prison?
>> It's the main too much volume. The
guards took one look at me and said,
"Yeah, that's a bitch." and toss me
right in.
>> Happened to me one time, too. When they
sent me to a stallion prison, I ran that
[__]
>> Mod limestone, you're here, too.
>> We've been standing here for 3 hours
hoping you would notice us, but you
never did. It's probably because we
resemble rocks.
>> They caught us smuggling rocks across
county lines. Sandstone. Very illegal
stuff.
>> Wowee. Zoe.
>> So, what the hell are you in here for?
I'm here for mass moto with deadly use
of a ferris wheel.
>> Oh, thank God. I thought you were gay.
Well, since you're not, you should be
out by next week.
>> This is perfect. We've got muscle, some
rock experts, and the captain of the
royal guard. Do you know what this
means?
>> We won't struggle to find sex partners.
>> No, we've got everything we need to bust
our way out of here.
>> Like, hell no. I'm going to serve my
time and walk out of here like the
innocent pliable girl they think I am.
And it's going to work as long as I
don't have to take off my pants. That's
hiding my mast.
>> Time to wash up, ladies. Eat your beans
and milk and hit those showers.
>> Look who went and dropped the goods.
Come on, shiny. You ain't going to waste
it all, are you?
>> Yeah. Pick up the soap, white, boy.
>> [__] [__] What the hell happened to
your face?
>> I think I fell asleep next to a candle.
Did I freaking ask, [__] Give me your
tots.
>> Hey, ladies, are there any free seats?
I'm a feminist now, so I'm technically
one of the [__]
>> Sure, you can sit next to us. This table
is for ponies considered to be born
wrong and you do consider yourself a
feminist.
>> So, um, the monster mash is happening in
the catacombs tonight. Anyone here in
the market for a short king?
No one. Cool. That's quite all right. I
was asking for a friend anyway.
>> Hey, Flawless. Did any pony ask you to
the dance yet?
>> Nah, no pony trusts mirror ponies, and I
don't really want to spend all night
standing in the corner alone, so I'm not
going. Why are we stressing ourselves
out about the dance? We're literally the
weird kids at a monster school. There is
literally no hope for any of us.
>> Changeling drone 13,420
is right. Why don't we just hang out in
the courtyard tonight instead? We could
steal snacks and throw things at couples
as they walk by.
>> That sounds fun. Y'all wait here. I'm
going to get some mac and cheese pizza.
Come on out, Belle. It's really not that
big of a deal.
>> Yo, hold up. Are we talking about the
situation or his member's size? Well, I
guess both are scientifically applicable
in this situation. Carry on.
I came in to take a dump. Why is every
pony in the bathroom? Belle's skirt was
torn off and now he's crying because
everyone saw his junk.
>> Damn, sounds rough. Was it at least 4
in?
>> No way.
>> Belle, can I say something?
>> Who are you?
>> I'm Spike, Twilight's best friend.
>> My dog ears can hear you whispering
heinous lies, you dumb [__]
>> I heard you crying from the other side
of the bathroom like a little girl while
I was cutting a fat steaming turd in my
butt crack. You shouldn't worry about
what happened, dude. We all go through
some cringe [__] Like I remember one
time when I went to the gym and people
laughed at the sheer girth of my own
balls and how I was so shredded that my
muscles tore through my tank top that
was stained gray with my sweat. I
dragged my balls crying all the way
home. And you know what I did when I got
home?
>> What did you do?
>> I woke up drunk the next morning with a
rope around my neck and a wooden stool
knocked down next to me. So the rope
must have snapped because I'm too fat.
God must have been like, "A yo, Spike,
my this ain't yo day, my homeboy,
because you gots to be there to help out
a brother from another mother."
>> Spike is right. And besides, your thing
was like really small. So, I don't think
the people standing at the further end
of the cafeteria could see it anyway.
Like, imagine if you had a normalsized
one or, god forbid, a really, really big
one. Now, that would have been way worse
because then people would have seen it,
but they didn't see yours because it was
so incredibly tiny.
Well, my little ponies, we gave him the
best words of encouragement that we
possibly could as females. Let's make
like a pair of sweaty balls and bounce.
Wow, she's really pretty. I wonder if I
have a shot with her. Excuse me.
Uh, I promise I don't normally dress
like this, so check it. Your playing is
awesome. There's going to be a dance in
the catacombs tonight. And I was
wondering if some pony asked you yet.
Well, if not, um, how about going with
me?
>> Yeah. Okay,
>> great. It starts at 7:00. I'll I'll see
you there, I guess.
You're dead. You died.
>> Yeah, I guess I did, huh?
>> A thousand years ago.
>> Wow. Has it really been that long? Well,
now that I think about it, I guess I
have been haunting you for centuries.
>> Are you really here, Star, or am I just
imagining things again? Starcatcher,
I miss you. I wish things didn't have to
change.
I wish I wish I could go to that that
time.
>> Spending your life worshiping the past
won't bring it back. It just steals time
from the pony sitting here now. You're
older than I was, Skye. Wiser than I
ever got the chance to become. You
survived things I couldn't have even
imagined facing. And every hour you
spend mourning me is an hour being taken
away from you.
Inside I feel nothing. Am I broken? Or
was I always this empty?
>> No, you weren't always like this.
Then what is wrong with me? Why can't I
feel anything?
>> The day Skywishes died was the day she
was truly gone.
>> What walks the earth now, what you are,
is not the Skywishes Starcatcher and
Trixie Bell cherished, but a sad husk of
her remains. Simply carrying her face.
The essence that made you you didn't
stay. It went somewhere
>> inside of a Philly named Twilight
Sparkle.
>> Twilight Sparkle.
>> That Twilight Sparkle took everything
and left me with nothing.
>> Everything you were, your hopes and
dreams.
>> I wish that it hurt more than it does.
Hey, Belle. What's the matter? Did your
date stand you up?
>> Shut up. She'll be here any second. She
probably just got lost on the way to the
catacombs.
>> I'm sorry, you guys. I just can't keep
it a secret anymore.
>> What are you saying? Well, Princess
Celestia found a pile of dust next to a
salt spear in her office just before the
dance, as well as a pair of clothes that
kind of look like they belong to a
vampire. I am like so so sorry.
Damn. Well, I can't honestly say it's
the first time some pony selfdeleted to
get out of a date with me, but it is
strange it keeps happening since I am
really sexy. And I can prove it because
my last selfie on Instagram got 11
likes. Can one of you go get me a beer?
I want to get drunk.
Why are the zombie and dragons hanging
out together outside the gymnasium?
That's kind of sus. They must be up to
something. I should get close and figure
out what they're talking about, but I'll
need some kind of disguise.
There we are. This should do the trick.
What up, my fellow dragon? Who the hell
are you, ugly [__] I know like all of
the dragons in the world because those
horse [__] made sure there was only
like three of us left. Can you believe
how those ponies made themselves the
most dominant species on the planet just
because they think they're better?
>> I'm Flawless Spark. Uh, Spark Fang,
>> I don't give a [__] Anyway, it's the
blue vampire and her dog [__] Those
fugly [__] are going to get what's
coming to them for dating outside of
their own kind. The zombies are going to
dump holy water on them. And I'm here to
make sure it goes swimmingly because I
am a racist and I revel in others
undeserved misfortune.
A yo spike, don't move up on us so fast.
Legit thought you were another autistic
white boy with a blickie.
>> Spike, is that you?
>> Flawless Sparkle Moon, what are you
doing here? Acting like a dragon.
>> Why are you wearing a bikini? You know
what? I don't want to know. Do you know
the dragons and zombies are about to
dump holy water on Trixie and Twilight?
>> Originally, it was going to be pee, but
then I found out holy water is more
lethal to monsters, so I thought it
would be funny to see them burn and die.
>> Well, make them stop.
>> I'm not going to listen to someone ugly.
Now leave me alone. I have drinks to
serve to my friends on the football
team. Hey, delete that picture. I pooped
in these panties.
>> Screw you, [__]
>> Princess Luna, have all of the monsters
consolidated in the gymnasium like a
packed can of sardines?
>> Yeah, Twilight and Trixie just arrived.
Perfect. Seal the doors and open the
vents. It sucks balls to know that my
own student Twilight Sparkle is among
them. But sometimes the great amalite
can only be made with by breaking eggs.
>> What is she doing?
>> Dear God, the dance was just a ploy all
along. The real purpose of the dance was
to gather all of the monsters together
into one room so Princess Celestia can
fart in the air vent and suffocate them
all, thus eliminating monsters from
Equestria in one failed swoop.
>> Fractured must have known, which is why
she told us not to go to the dance
tonight. But if she did know, then why
is she still at the school?
>> It's basically a weapon made of salt. To
summon one, you have to do a ritual that
requires four hearts being placed at the
corners of a salt circle.
>> That's it. Fractured is planning on
using one monster from each group to use
them as a sacrifice to make a salt
spear.
>> Okay. Well, why don't we just not go?
>> I've been waiting for you. Flawless bro.
Quit aura farming for monstrous
sacrifices. That's what's needed to make
a salt spear. A vampire named Skywishes
was meant to be the last one. But then I
realized I didn't need her anymore. So I
talked Sky Wishes into breaking into
Celestia's office for me to steal the
only one in the building so that it
couldn't be used against me. And she
actually did it. Ponies are easy to
manipulate when they have nothing left
to live for. But then it hit me. Why
stop at one? I mean, I still have three
monsters ready and waiting to be
sacrificed.
>> If you have one, then you don't need
another.
>> I know. The second one is for you. Think
about it. Nobody could stop us. You and
me could rule all of Equestria together.
You agree with me. Everyone else looks
at us like we're mistakes. But we're
perfect. Nevertheless, you only have
three. You're still missing a vampire
sacrifice.
>> Oh, I never needed a vampire to be here
in person. That's why I paid Sky Wishes
a little visit. Before she did the deed,
I took something from her. something she
didn't need anymore. This should be more
than enough to conduct the ritual.
>> Hurry up and open the door before we all
suffocate to death.
>> Yeah, it is getting incredibly stinky.
It's no use all of the doors are locked.
Probably the dragons who dumped the
bucket of water on my head.
>> No, it has to be the zombies. They're
locking us all in here to starve because
they're the only ones who don't need to
eat to survive. Like, shut up, you
specialed kid. As if any of us zombies
have the brain capacity to operate a
locking mechanism. Clearly, this is the
vampire's handiwork. Every pony knows
they're most likely to engage in
elaborate architectural sabotage due to
their historical preference for Gothic
structures. That's [__] Of course,
you would defend your vampire
girlfriend, you species traitor. No pony
listen to the werewolves. They're
breeding with enemy factions.
>> Will all of you ponies listen to
yourselves?
>> Shut the hell up, fat [__] You're all
building entire criminal profiles based
on stereotypes. Where do you think we
are? North America. This is the magical
realm of Equestria. For what reason
would we have to secretly go behind each
other's backs and locked doors? Creature
segregation is what helped Equestria
live through a thousand years of peace.
So, if we have problems with each other,
we're going to announce it with our
whole chest. Not like some little poopy
baby [__] that alone should tell us
all that none of us are to blame for
this evilness. Am I right?
WOOHOO! YAHOO!
YAHOO!
>> CELESTIA! The monsters are breaking
through the gymnasium doors. Twilight
rallied the ponies together through the
unity of shared bigotry. And I didn't
account for the possibility of two
ponies working together to push a door
open. "We're going home, Luna. Press the
red button that launches a nuclear bomb
to destroy the school. We can't afford
the public finding out that I just tried
to lock thousands of ponies in a room
and farted on them. Especially if I
still wish for my face to remain on
Ponyville's marble slab of individuals
who did many extraordinary things.
>> Twilight, it's a ritual. You can't stop
it. The only way to save someone is to
replace them.
>> Twilight, wait. Don't be a hero.
>> Ow. What the [__] Twilight?
>> All four of their souls are now trapped
inside that spear. And what are you
going to do with it? What am I going to
do with it? That should be obvious.
I'm going to kill you.
REALLY
love me. You really me.
You say that there is no other. I am the
only one.
You're just a monster.
>> All the world does is create monsters.
But at least some of us are willing to
admit it.
>> What's that? A nuclear bomb. You fight
for them and this is what they send you
in return. A bomb big enough to erase
every monster in this school. And you're
still fighting so hard to protect this
world. They will never accept you as one
of their own. To them, you're just a
monster like me. And monsters don't
love.
>> Where the hell are we?
>> I would think that's obvious, [__]
This is the world of salt. It's like
purgatory for modern Sonic fans when
they finally off themselves as they all
do because they are salty that modern
Sonic the Hedgehog media majorly sucks
big hairy balls compared to the hit 1999
series Sonic Underground made by Dee
Entertainment.
>> It's almost like as soon as you start
watching modern Sonic, it's all downhill
from there.
>> And how do we get out? The doorway is
freely open to us because unlike modern
Sonic fans, we don't hate our own lives
because we all understand the greatness
of Sonic Underground, which we
faithfully worship with our whole
hearts. The true path to happiness, one
could say that modern Sonic will never
be able to understand because they would
rather drown themselves in the poop that
Sega shits out in front of them.
>> I know. Somehow I've always known that
Sonic Underground would save us. It's
like Sonic Underground never gives up on
us, even when all things else will.
>> So, what happens now?
>> You know, you can't destroy me. I always
come back.
>> You were going to let the missile blow
up the school and kill everyone.
>> Of course I did. I did it because I'm
your bad half dumbass. That's literally
what I'm supposed to do. It's what
people expect from me.
>> Because you're evil.
>> You think I don't know what I am? I'm
the side no pony wants inside of them.
The part that every pony hates because
it's bad. The part that that gets people
into trouble and that's meant to be
hidden away.
I'm I'm evil. I'm evil. Because if
ponies are scared of me, at least
they're forced to acknowledge me.
>> Don't Don't you dare pity me. Fate chose
me to be evil. Fate chooses us all
fractured. The only question is what
for? It chose you to follow the path of
the insane murderer. And it chose me to
bring your evil ways to an end. You will
not harm me because I am your friend.
>> You'd really want to be friends with me.
Sure,
>> I'll be your friend. We'll all be your
friends if that's okay.
>> All All I have ever wanted was a friend.
A
>> in exchange for us being sworn to
secrecy about the nuclear attack within
Ponyville borders, Princess Celestia
offered to graduate everyone in school
and treated every pony to some hot and
ready Little Caesars, so long as Trixie
also used her magic over illusions to
completely undo the monsterification of
every pony in the town.
>> Flawless Sparkle Moon.
>> Vampires lost the ability to turn into
bats and drink blood. Werewolves lost
their fangs and zombies are no longer
undead.
>> Trixie Lullemoon.
>> Goodbye every pony. I'll remember you
all in therapy.
Marionette.
Changeling drone 13,420.
Fracture.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Thanks, Mary. I need to tell you
something. You set my face on fire,
didn't you?
>> I'm sorry. I just hate how pretty you
are when it's not. What if you started
getting compliments? Someone else can
take you so easily.
>> Pooky, I'm not mad. You're not? You
could literally burn my face off a
thousand times over and I would still
forgive you because you told me the
truth. Being honest is the truest way to
a healthy relationship.
Do you want to help me put on my burn
cream?
And this is Kachik, Aisha, Shiu, Yusul,
and Lupe, otherwise known as the Core 6.
If you're going to start an epic
collection of Neopets like the one I
have, you're going to have to
familiarize with these ones first. Which
one is your favorite?
>> Aisha is pretty cool, I guess, like an
alien.
Seems like the special guest Trixie
called over has arrived.
>> God, I really hope they like my shitty
ass music.
>> Of course they will, Drake. Everyone on
earth loves the head theme song to Drake
and Josh. It's like the only good song
you ever made.
>> Damn. You know what, [__] For a fat
ass, you're actually right for once in
your shitty life. Besides, I doubt
horses actually know what good music
sounds like. Like, I haven't seen a
single pony listening to Britney Spears
since we arrived. So, they might not
realize how [__] my music actually is.
>> That's the spirit break. Now, head on
inside and give those pony [__] the
epic concert they deserve.
>> Oh, boy. Is it Hatsune Miko?
>> What's up, Rake Bell?
>> They're talking about me. Shut the hell
up, you fat [__]
>> Or maybe someone else famous like Taylor
Swift. Hopefully, it's not Drake Bell
because that would suck.
Well, let's get this [__] over so I can
hurry back over to Mexico.
>> Oh my god. Is that one of the BTS
members? No, he's a white guy.
>> Sup, [__] Your parents told me you
turned over a new leaf, so I decided to
pop up in this [__] and sing you the
only song that I made that people care
about. The Drake and Josh theme song
from the hit TV show Drake and Josh.
>> I don't know what that is. The Great and
Powerful has connection with many other
failed D performers because she also
sucks. It only cost $14 because it's
Drake Bell. I wanted to get Marina and
the Diamonds to sing Primadana Girl, but
she wouldn't answer Trixie's calls.
>> Hey, that's C rate to you. Don't forget
I'm still mildly famous in Mexico for
some reason as Drake Campana.
>> Oh, I get it. C is in Kana.
>> No C because my music is crap.
that it seems so simple, but I found a
way. I found a way and I only
>> Yo, did Drake Bell just crap?
>> You know what? If being on the side of
good means you get $14 concerts every
once in a while. Maybe this is a life I
can get used to after all.
>> Why is Drake Bell pooping in my living
room?
Trixie paid him $14 and some Mountain
Dew for a private concert. He's
desperate. Didn't he plead guilty in
2021 to charges of inappropriate
relationships with underage fans?
>> Oh, Trixie didn't know that. Trixie just
likes the show Drake and Josh.
Understandable.
>> Well, every pony is having a good time,
so I guess we can kick him out after the
song.
to be free. You know, you got to be
photograph.
No surrender.
Maybe you want me.
Sup, [__] I'm Drake Bell from the
Nickelodeon phenomenon known as Drake
and Josh, and I'm here to personally ask
you to subscribe to Tamers 1 12345's
YouTube channel because it's like so
close to getting to 100,000 and [__]
So, hit that subscribe button when I
count down from 10. 10 9 8 5 4 3 2 1.
Did you hit that subscribe button?
Thanks. It really means a lot to me. By
the way, there's also a [__] ton of
gifts on Patreon, so you can go over
there also. Later, [__]